{
    "subject": "resource/Funkdoobiest",
    "predicate": "http://xmlns.com/foaf/0.1/name",
    "object": "Funkdoobiest",
    "human_readable": "The name of Funkdoobiest is Funkdoobiest.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9725561738014221,
            "question": "What is the name of Funkdoobiest?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9053921103477478,
            "question": "Who are the members of Funkdoobiest?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9017981290817261,
            "question": "Is Funkdoobiest a person or a group?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8577127456665039,
            "question": "Where is Funkdoobiest from?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8532432317733765,
            "question": "Could you tell me more about Funkdoobiest?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8490422368049622,
            "question": "What are some of the characteristics of Funkdoobiest's music?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.845714271068573,
            "question": "What genre of music is associated with Funkdoobiest?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8455828428268433,
            "question": "Are there any famous songs by Funkdoobiest?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.838356614112854,
            "question": "Has Funkdoobiest collaborated with other artists?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8285144567489624,
            "question": "When was Funkdoobiest popular?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The name of Funkdoobiest is Funkdoobiest.",
            "html": "dbpedia_9059_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Has Funkdoobiest collaborated with other artists?",
            "html": "dbpedia_9059_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Are there any famous songs by Funkdoobiest?",
            "html": "dbpedia_9059_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What genre of music is associated with Funkdoobiest?",
            "html": "dbpedia_9059_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9059_14.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9059_20.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9059_25.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9059_37.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9059_39.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9059_50.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9059_69.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9059_70.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9059_71.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9059_74.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe query states that the name of Funkdoobiest is Funkdoobiest, which is consistent across multiple documents provided in the context information. Therefore, the answer is \"yes\"."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Most Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}